A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.26 (A2000) FA470
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2000.031: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1987-1998; AC.2000.031; 7.2 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3320, R3320A, R3321-R3324.; 6 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3320, R3320A, R3321-R3324.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.031.1
    - 930040-28 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - CURRENT STATUS, CONSTRAINTS, AND POTENTIAL OF UPLAND RICE PRODUCTION, 1993-1994; 1998 (Box R3320)
    - 930044-33 - CHENGDU INSTITUTE OF BIOLOGICAL PRODUCTS (CHINA) - PLANNING VACCINE PRODUCTION FACILITY, 1993-1997 (Box R3320)
    - RF 93044 A 36 - VECOL (EMPRESA COLOMBIANA DE PRODUCTOS VETERINARIOS S.A.) - HUMAN RABIES VACCINE PROJECT, 1991-1999 (Box R3320)
    - RF 93044 A 39 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - STUDY OF JAPANESE ENCEPHALITIS VACCINE, 1993-1997 (Box R3320)
    - 930050-151 - MORALES, SYLVIA - "REAL MEN AND OTHER MIRACLES", 1994-1997 (Box R3320)
    - RF 93050 A 173 - PONCE, MAGALY - PORCELAIN FLOWERS, 1995-1996 (Box R3320)
    - RF 93053 A 167 - VILLAGE OF THE ARTS AND HUMANITIES INC - "FLYING OVER WALLS", 1993-1998 (Box R3320)
    - RF 93053 A 168 - SANG-FROID LTD. -"THE OPIUM WAR", 1991-1998 (Box R3320)
    - RF 93053 A 171 - SEVEN STAGES- LOOKING BACKWARD, WORKING FORWARD, 1994-1998 (Box R3320A)
    - RF 93053 A 179 - APPALSHOP - ZUNI-APPALACHIAN COLLABORATION, 1994-1997 (Box R3320A)
    - RF 93053 A 180 - AXIS DANCE TROUPE - "VISIBLE DIFFERENCES/HIDDEN HISTORIES", 1994-1998 (Box R3320A)
    - RF 93053 A 182 - DANCING IN THE STREET - CITY WATER TUNNEL # 3, 1990; 1994-1998 (Box R3320A)
    - RF 93053 A 186 - GAMELAN SEKAR JAYA- BALINESE/AMERICAN COLLABORATIVE WORKS, 1994-1996 (Box R3321)
    - RF 93053 A 187 - GOTHAM DANCE -TINY SISTERS, 1994-1996 (Box R3321)
    - RF 93053 A 188 - HELENA PRESENTS - COMMISSIONING AND RESIDENCY TO CREATE NEW WORK, 1994-1997 (Box R3321)
    - RF 93053 A 189 - JAPANESE CULTURAL ARTS CENTER- THE GOBLINS, 1994-1997 (Box R3321)
    - RF 93053 A 190 - LIFE ON THE WATER- GENOCIDAL SUICIDE, 1994-1997 (Box R3321)
    - RF 93053 A 191 - MCCARTER THEATRE COMPANY - NEW PLAY FESTIVAL, 1994-1996 (Box R3321)
    - RF 93053 A 92 - MIAMI-DADE COMMUNITY COLLEGE - MIAMI X CHANGE (WOLFSON), 1994-1998 (Box R3321)
    - RF 93053 A 193 - MUSIC-THEATRE GROUP - YOU DON'T MISS WATER, 1994-1997 (Box R3321)
    - RF 93054 A 15 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (SAN DIEGO) - COMPUTER MUSIC RESIDENCY EXCHANGE PROGRAM, 1988-1997 (Box R3321)
    - RF 93054 A 16 - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - COMPUTER MUSIC COLLABORATIVE RESIDENCY AND EXCHANGE, 1987-1996 (Box R3321)
    - RF 93055 A 63 - URBAN STRATEGIES COUNCIL - PERSISTENT POVERTY PROJECTS, 1986-1995; 1998; Total of 5 folders in Boxes R3321 and R3322. (Box R3321)
    - RF 93055 A 63 - URBAN STRATEGIES COUNCIL - PERSISTENT POVERTY PROJECTS, 1986-1995; 1998; Total of 5 folders in Boxes R3321 and R3322. (Box R3322)
    - RF 93055 A 63 - URBAN STRATEGIES COUNCIL - PERSISTENT POVERTY PROJECTS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIALS, 1986-1995; 1998; Total of 5 folders in Boxes R3322 and R3323. (Box R3322)
    - RF 93055 A 63 - URBAN STRATEGIES COUNCIL - PERSISTENT POVERTY PROJECTS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIALS, 1986-1995; 1998; Total of 5 folders in Boxes R3322 and R3323. (Box R3323)
    - RF 93055 A 64 - PARTNERSHIP FOR HOPE - PERSISTENT POVERTY PROJECTS, 1987-1996; Total of 5 folders in Boxes R3323 and R3324. (Box R3323)
    - RF 93055 A 64 - PARTNERSHIP FOR HOPE - PERSISTENT POVERTY PROJECTS, 1987-1996; Total of 5 folders in Boxes R3323 and R3324. (Box R3324)
    - RF 93055 A 64 - PARTNERSHIP FOR HOPE - PERSISTENT POVERTY PROJECTS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1987-1996; 2 folders. (Box R3324)
- AC.2000.034: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1986-1999; AC.2000.034; 1.2 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, Box R3325.; 1 standard record storage box, Box R3325.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.034.1
    - RF 93055 #68 - URBAN INSTITUTE - HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES IN SAN ANTONIO, 1996-1997 (Box R3325)
    - RF 93060 A 1 - NATIONAL EPIDEMIOLOGY BOARD OF THAILAND, 1986-1998; 2 folders. (Box R3325)
    - RF 93062 - (FELLOWSHIP AWARD TERMINATIONS) ? POPULATION SCIENCES, 1993-1994 (Box R3325)
    - RF 93063 A 77 - BEIJING MEDICAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - WATER CHANNELS IN MALE AND FEMALE REPRODUCTIVE SYSTEMS, 1994-1997 (Box R3325)
    - RF 93065 A 66 - MAZINGIRA INSTITUTE (KENYA) - SCIENCE AND MATHEMATICS IN GIRLS' AND WOMEN'S LIVES, 1993-1997 (Box R3325)
    - 930066-35 - SULLEIMAN, RASHID SEIF - CHILDREN'S SCIENCE PROJECT ON THE NIGHT SKY IN ZANZIBAR, 1994-1996 (Box R3325)
    - RF 93066 A 48 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - SEMINAR ON PROMOTION OF LITERACY IN SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY, 1995; 1999 (Box R3325)
    - RF 93066 A 49 - FORUM FOR AFRICAN WOMEN EDUCATIONALISTS (KENYA) - EXHIBIT OF AFRICAN TOYS THAT DEVELOP SCIENCE AND MATHEMATICS, 1995-1997 (Box R3325)
    - RF 93067 A 10 - ASIAN AMERICAN RENAISSANCE - IN THE MIX, 1995-1999 (Box R3325)
    - RF 93067 A 11 - COALITION FOR IMMIGRANT REFUGEE RIGHTS AND SERVICES - "CHINESE AND LATINA IMMIGRANT LEADERSHIP TRAINING & ORGANIZING/EDUCATIONAL CAMPAIGN", 1995-1997 (Box R3325)
    - RF 93067 A 14 - HIGHLANDER RESEARCH AND EDUCATION CENTER - "CROSS-CULTURAL LABOR INITIATIVE", 1995-1999 (Box R3325)
- AC.2000.037: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1985-1999; AC.2000.037; 4.8 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3326-R3329.; 4 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3326-R3329.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.037.1
    - RF 93077 - OVERSEAS DEVELOPMENT COUNCIL - US AND DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1990-1996; 1999; 2 folders. (Box R3326)
    - RF 93078 A 2 - BANARAS HINDU UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - EFFECTS OF BREASTFEEDING ON FERTILITY IN RURAL NORTHERN INDIA, 1994-1999 (Box R3327)
    - 940001-232 - OHIO STATE UNIVERSITY RESEARCH FOUNDATION - NITROGEN ASSIMILATION AND PROLINE SYNTHESIS IN RICE, 1992-1999 (Box R3327)
    - 940001-241 - HUNAN HYBRID RICE RESEARCH CENTER (CHINA) - HETEROSIS IN RICE; IDENTIFICATION OF QUANTITATIVE TRAIT LOCI (QTLs) FROM WILD RICE SPECIES, 1993-1998 (Box R3327)
    - 940001-272 - BIOTECHNOLOGY RESEARCH CENTER (VIETNAM)- STRENGTHENING RESEARCH CAPABILITY IN RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1994-1998 (Box R3327)
    - 940001-282 - POONSAK MEKWATANAKARN - CHARACTERIZE GENETIC STRUCTURE AND VIRULENCE DIVERSITY OF RICE BLAST FUNGUS, 1994-1998 (Box R3327)
    - 940001-293 - UNIVERSITY OF FLORIDA- BETAINE ACCUMULATION IN RICE, 1994-1996 (Box R3327)
    - 940001-294 - INTERNATIONAL SERVICE FOR THE ACQUISITION OF AGRI-BIOTECH APPLICATIONS- 1994-97 TRANSFER OF BIOTECHNOLOGY FROM JAPAN TO OTHER RICE-DEPENDENT COUNTRIES IN ASIA, 1994-1997 (Box R3327)
    - 940006-14 - INDIAN ASSOCIATION OF PARLIAMENTARIANS ON POPULATION AND DEVELOPMENT - SURVEY ON POPULATION ISSUES, 1994-1996 (Box R3327)
    - 940006-16 - AMERICAN UNIVERSITY - COLLEGE OF LAW - CONFERENCE ON INTERNATIONAL LAW AND WOMEN'S REPRODUCTIVE RIGHTS, 1994-1996 (Box R3327)
    - RF 94006 A 24 - POPULATION COUNCIL - MULTIPLE COMPONENTS OF POPULATION GROWTH, 1994-1997 (Box R3327)
    - RF 94006 A 30 - FAMILY CARE INTERNATIONAL - REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH ISSUES AT FOURTH WORLD CONFERENCE ON WOMEN, 1995-1996 (Box R3327)
    - RF 94010 A 559 - UNIVERSITY OF FLORIDA - HUMANITIES RESIDENCY PROGRAM, 1992-1998 (Box R3327)
    - RF 94011 A17 - MEDIA FOR DEVELOPMENT TRUST (ZIMBABWE) - CONFERENCE/WORKSHOP ON AFRICAN FILM AND VIDEO DISTRIBUTION, 1994-1997 (Box R3328)
    - RF 94011 A 18 - THAPONG INTERNATIONAL ARTISTS' WORKSHOP (BOTSWANA) - PARTICIPATION OF FOREIGN ARTISTS AT WORKSHOP, 1992-1996 (Box R3328)
    - 940012-104 - A:SHIWI A:WAN MUSEUM AND HERITAGE CENTER - PUBLISH POSITION PAPERS ON TRIBAL EGO-MUSEUMS ISSUES, 1994-1997 (Box R3328)
    - RF 94012 A 110 - MID-AMERICA ARTS ALLIANCE - TRAVELLING EXHIBITION BETYE SAAR: PERSONAL ICONS, 1994-1997 (Box R3328)
    - RF 94012 A 112 - SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTION - EXHIBITION: "AN OCEAN APART: VIETNAMESE CONTEMPORARY ART FROM THE UNITED STATES AND VIETNAM", 1994-1998 (Box R3328)
    - RF 94012 A 116 - SOUTHEASTERN CENTER FOR CONTEMPORARY ART - 1995 ARTIST AND COMMUNTY PROJECTS, 1994-1996 (Box R3328)
    - RF 94012 A 118 - COUNCIL FOR CREATIVE PROJECTS - "HECHO EN CUBA: 1959-1994", 1994-1996 (Box R3328)
    - RF 94014 A 119 - CONTEMPORARY ARTS CENTER, INC. (NEW ORLEANS) - INTERDISCIPLINARY ARTISTS, 1985-1997 (Box R3328)
    - RF 94014 A 125 - 80 LANGTON STREET- INTERDISCIPLINARY ARTISTS, 1985-1997 (Box R3329)
    - RF 94014 A 129 - FLORIDA DANCE ASSOCIATION - NEW WORKS COMMISSIONING PROGRAM, 1993-1997 (Box R3329)
    - RF 94014 A 132 - PYRAMID ARTS CENTER - INTERDISCIPLINARY ARTISTS, 1990-1997 (Box R3329)
    - RF 94017 - A 6 - FORT WORTH INDEPENDENT SCHOOL DISTRICT - BUILDING AN INFRASTRUCTURE FOR PROFESSIONALDEVELOPMENT, 1994-1997 (Box R3329)
    - RF 94017 A 13 - MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY - HOLMES GROUP RESTRUCTURING ACTIVITIES, 1995 (Box R3329)
    - 940020-41 - MALAWI - AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH (DEPT. OF) - MAIZE RESEARCH OF THE SOILS COMMODITY TEAM, 1994-1995; 1998 (Box R3329)
    - 940020-46 - ZIMBABWE LANDS, AGRICULTURE AND RURAL DEVELOPMENT (MINISTRY OF) - MAP CROP AND SOIL NUTRIENT STATUS FOR IMPROVED FERTILIZER RECOMMENDATIONS, 1993-1996 (Box R3329)
    - 940020-47 - ZIMBABWE - LANDS, AGRICULTURE AND RURAL DEVELOPMENT (MINISTRY OF) - CROP SEQUENCE AND FERTILITY MANAGEMENT IN MAIZE, SUNFLOWER AND GROUNDNUT SYSTEMS ON SANDY SOILS, 1994-1996 (Box R3329)
    - 940020-48 - ZIMBABWE - LANDS, AGRICULTURE AND RURAL DEVELOPMENT (MINISTRY OF) - SOIL FERTILITY MANAGEMENT THROUGH RELAY GREEN MANURING, 1994-1996 (Box R3329)
    - 940020-49 - ZIMBABWE - LANDS AGRICULTURE AND RURAL DEVELOPMENT (MINISTRY OF) - IMPROVE FEED SUPPLY TO DRAFT ANIMALS BY USING PERENNIAL LEGUMES, 1994-1996 (Box R3329)
    - 940020-50 - ZIMBABWE - LANDS, AGRICULTURE AND DEVELOPMENT (MINIISTRY OF) - EVALUATION OF CONSERVATION TILLAGE IN SMALL-SCALE FARMING AREAS, 1994-1996 (Box R3329)
    - RF 94020 A 63 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE {NIGERIA) - TRAINING COURSE ON LABORATORY EQUIPMENT MAINTENANCE, 1994-1997 (Box R3329)
    - 940021-2 - CENTER FOR THE APPLICATION OF MOLECULAR BIOLOGY TO INTERNATIONAL AGRICULTURE (CAMBIA) (AUSTRALIA)- DEVELOPMENT OF THE GUS REPORTER GENE SYSTEM, 1993-1997 (Box R3329)
    - 940021-5 - UNIVERSITY OF GUELPH (CANADA) - TRANSFORMATION OF CASSAVA BY COCULTIVATION OF AXILLARY NODES WITH AGROBACTERIUM, 1994-1997 (Box R3329)
- AC.2000.040: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1979-2000; AC.2000.040; 3.6 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3330-R3332.; 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3330-R3332.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.040.1
    - RF 94023 A 49 - UNIVERSIDAD AUTONOMA CHAPINGO (MEXICO) - TESTING AND VALIDATION OF THE FELSM PROJECT, 1995-1997 (Box R3330)
    - RF 94023 A 50 - UNIVERSIDAD AUTONOMA DE YUCATAN (MEXICO) - ON-FARM RESEARCH IN SAHCABA COMMUNITY, 1993-1997 (Box R3330)
    - RF 94023 A 51 - COLEGIO DE POSTGRADUADOS (MEXICO) - THIRD ANNUAL MEETING OF THE NATURAL RESOURCES/MEXICO NETWORK, 1995 (Box R3330)
    - RF 94024 A 82 - UNIVERSITY OF CHEIKH ANTA DIOP (SENEGAL) - HIV PREVENTION AND CONTROL, 1994-1997 (Box R3330)
    - RF 94024 A 90 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - COMMUNITY-BASED STD INTERVENTIONS IN AFRICA, 1995-1997 (Box R3330)
    - RF 94025 A 26 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - INSTITUTE OF MEDICINE - BIOTECHNOLOGY AND CONTRACEPTIVE RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT, 1992-1997 (Box R3330)
    - RF 94026 A 7 - INDIAN INSTITUTE OF SCIENCE - PURA VILLAGE COMMUNITY BIOGAS, 1994-1996; 1999 (Box R3330)
    - RF 94026 A 9 - SOLUZ, INC. - STUDY FOR A SOLAR ELECTRIC DELIVERY COMPANY IN THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC, 1993-1999 (Box R3330)
    - 1994-0030 - POVERTY AND RACE RESEARCH ACTION COUNCIL - RACE AND POVERTY, 1989-1996; 2 folders. (Box R3331)
    - RF 94031 A 34 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - ECONOMICS OF FERTILIZER USE IN MAIZE PRODUCTION AMONG SMALLHOLDER FARMERS, 1993-1998 (Box R3331)
    - RF 94031 A 53 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - HIGH QUALITY DRY SEASON FORAGE, 1995-1997 (Box R3331)
    - RF 94031 A 53 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - AFRICAN CASSAVA MOSAIC GEMINIVIRUS, 1995-1998 (Box R3331)
    - RF 94034 A 461 - WEST CHINA UNIVERSITY OF MEDICAL SCIENCES - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY UNIT, 1993-1998; 2 folders. (Box R3331)
    - RF 94034 A 465 - INTERNATIONAL EPIDEMIOLOGICAL ASSOCIATION - REGIONAL MEETINGS IN EGYPT, CHINA AND ZIMBABWE, 1993-1996 (Box R3332)
    - RF 94034 A 467 - HOSPTAL GENERAL DE MEXICO - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY UNIT, 1983-1997 (Box R3332)
    - RF 94034 A 467 - HOSPTAL GENERAL DE MEXICO - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY UNIT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1983-1997; 3 folders. (Box R3332)
    - RF 94034 A 470 - MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY, 1979-1996; 2000 (Box R3332)
    - RF 94034 A 470 - MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1979-1996; 2000 (Box R3332)
    - RF 94034 A 472 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY UNIT, 1987-1997 (Box R3332)
- AC.2000.044: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1984-2000; AC.2000.044; 3.6 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3333-R3335.; 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3333-R3335.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.044.1
    - RF 94034 A 474 - ADDIS ABABA UNIVERSITY - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY UNIT, 1984-2000 (Box R3333)
    - RF 94034 A 20 - TULANE UNIVERSITY - SCHOOLS OF PUBLIC HEALTH WITHOUT WALLS, 1992-1997 (Box R3333)
    - RF 94035 A 31 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - ENABLE FIELD COORDINATOR TO PARTICIPATE IN WORKSHOP, 1996-1997 (Box R3333)
    - RF 94035 A 33 - WEST CHINA UNIVERSITY OF MEDICAL SCIENCES - WORKSHOP ON BURDEN OF DISEASE, 1995-1996 (Box R3333)
    - RF 94039 A 7 - DARTMOUTH COLLEGE - BC CONFERENCE - PRINT ISLAM AND CIVIC PLURALISM, 1994-1996 (Box R3333)
    - RF 94039 A 11 - LEBANESE CENTER FOR POLICY STUDIES - PLURALISM ISSUES IN MUSLIM SOCIETIES, 1993-1998 (Box R3333)
    - RF 94039 A 15 - ISTANBUL ALUMNI FOUNDATION OF FACULTY OF POLITICAL SCIENCE (TURKEY) - TRANSITION OF TURKISH AND MAGHREBI SOCIETIES, 1994-1997 (Box R3333)
    - RF 94039 A 16 - UNITED NATIONS - SEMINAR ON ARAB MEDIA, 1995-1996 (Box R3333)
    - RF 94039 A 18 - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL HISTORY FOUNDATION OF TURKEY - PHASE II ISTANBUL MUSEUM AND SOCIAL HISTORY CENTER, 1995-1996 (Box R3333)
    - RF 94039 A 21 - PALESTIAN ACADEMIC SOCIETY FOR THE STUDY OF INTERNATIONAL AFFAIRS (ISRAEL) - DIALOGUE PROGRAMME ON BUILDING PALESTINIAN CIVIL SOCIETY, 1995-1997 (Box R3333)
    - RF 94039 A 23 - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL HISTORY FOUNDATION OF TURKEY - CIVIL SOCIETY IN ISTANBUL AND ASSOCIATIONAL LIFE IN MUSLIM CITIES, 1995-1997 (Box R3333)
    - RF 94039 A 24 - LEBANESE CENTER FOR POLICY STUDIES (LEBANON) - CIVIL SOCIETY IN BEIRUT, 1995-1998 (Box R3333)
    - RF 94039 #26 - AL-URDUN AL-JADID RESEARCH CENTER (JORDAN)- CIVIL SOCIETY IN AMMAN, 1995-1997 (Box R3334)
    - RF 94039 #27 - PROLOGUES: THE MAGHREBI REVIEW OF BOOKS (MOROCCO) - CIVIL SOCIETY IN CASABLANCA, 1995-1998 (Box R3334)
    - RF 94043 A 195 - NEW YORK THEATRE WORKSHOP - NOTHING FOREVER, 1994-1997 (Box R3334)
    - RF 94043 A 196 - PACIFIC SYMPHONY ASSOCIATION - A MUSICAL REFLECTION ON THE VIETNAM WAR, 1994-1996 (Box R3334)
    - RF 94043 A 198 - PERFORMANCE SPACE 122 - FEATHER AT THE FLAME, 1994-1997 (Box R3334)
    - RF 94043 A 199 - PREGONES TOURING PUERTO RICAN THEATRE COLLECTION- LA RUTA PANORAMICA: THE NORTHEASTERN LATINO CULTURAL CORRIDOR, 1994-1995 (Box R3334)
    - RF 94043 #200 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (BERKELEY) - "I WAS LOOKING AT THE CEILING AND THEN I SAW THE SKY", 1994-1995 (Box R3334)
    - RF 94043 #203 - WALKER ART CENTER - RESIDENCY PROJECT PERFORMANCE WORKSHOPS IN MINNEAPOLIS-ST. PAUL, 1994-1995 (Box R3334)
    - RF 94043 A 203 - TARA ARTS GROUP (ENGLAND) - ODYSSEY PROJECT WORKSHOP, 1994-1997 (Box R3334)
    - RF 94043 A 208 - UNIVERSITY OF LEEDS (ENGLAND) - ERITREA COMMUNITY BASED THEATRE PROJECT, 1994-1998 (Box R3334)
    - 940048 - REDISTRICTING CHALLENGES UNDER THE VOTING RIGHTS ACT, 1994-1995 (Box R3334)
    - RF 94048 A 5 - NAACP LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATIONAL FUND- REDISTRICTING CHALLENGES UNDER VOTING RIGHTS ACT, 1994-1995 (Box R3334)
    - RF 94049 A 175 - RODRIGUEZ, HUGO -THE RETURN, 1995-1997 (Box R3334)
    - RF 94049 A 176 - MORALES, ALFONSO - NOMADIC MEXICO, 1995-1997 (Box R3334)
    - RF 94049 A 177 - MARTINELLI, MIRELLA - LAND AND SEA, 1995-1996 (Box R3334)
    - RF 94049 A 178 - MOREIRA, RITA- THE OTHER AND I, 1995-1997 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 179 - SANTOS, EDER - INTRIGUING PEOPLE, 1995-1997 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 180 - REEVES, DANIEL - OBSESSIVE BECOMING, 1995-1997 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 181 - AIKIN, SUSANA - THE TRANSFORMATION, 1995-1996 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 182 - EYRE, CHRIS- "HE WHO CRAWLS ...", 1995-1996 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 183 - BRUNO, ELLEN - SLAVE GIRLS, 1995-1997 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 184 - BURDEAU, GEORGE - BACKBONE TO THE WORLD, 1995-1997 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 185 - MEISELAS, SUSAN - REMEMBERING KURD/STAN, 1995-1998 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 186 - MEKURIA, SALEM - DOCUMENTARY ? FRAGMENTS OF A MEMORIAL, 1995-1997 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 187 - XIAOLIAN PENG - BILLY HARLEM AND ME, 1995-1996 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 188 - ROBINSON, JONATHAN - OYE FAMILIA! A DIALOGUE WITH SOCIETY, 1991-1997 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 189 - NANJI, MEENA - A NET OF JEWELS, 1994-1997 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 190 - MANN, LISA - CAT CALLS, 1995-1997 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 191 - AVILA, CARLOS - FOTO-NOVELAS, 1994-1997 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 193 - CLARK, LARRY - FEATHER RIVER, 1995-2000 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 196 - FOUNDATION FOR INDEPENDENT VIDEO AND FILM, INC.- "INFORMATION SERVICES FOR THE 21ST CENTURY'', 1994-1997 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 200 - RESOLUTION - REIMAGINING AFRICA PROJECT, 1994-1996 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 201 - MEDIA FOR DEVELOPMENT TRUST (ZIMBABWE) ? ESTABLISH FILM AND VIDEO CENTER IN HARARE, 1995-1998 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94049 A 204 - NATIONAL ASIAN AMERICAN TELECOMMUNICATIONS ASSOCIATION- "LIVING ROOM FESTIVAL" - 1996 SEASON, 1995-1996 (Box R3335)
    - RF 94050 A 4 - AUTONOMOUS UNIVERSITY OF CHAPINGO (MEXICO) - IV INTERNATIONAL TRAINING COURSE ON AGROFORESTRY; CD-ROM LIBRARY, 1994-1997 (Box R3335)
- AC.2000.046: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1980-1998; AC.2000.046; 6 Cubic Feet 5 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3336-R3340.; 5 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3336-R3340.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.046.1
    - RF 94055 A 12 - PETROLEUM CORPORATION OF JAMAICA - HYDROPOWER PROJECTS, 1994-1995 (Box R3336)
    - RF 94056 #77 - CAMERINI, INC. - DOCUMENTRY FILM ON GIRLS EDUCATION IN AFRICA, 1993-1997 (Box R3336)
    - RF 94061 A 77 - TEATRO AVANTE - NEW YORK COMPONENT OF XTH INTERNATIONAL HISPANIC THEATRE FESTIVAL, 1994-1997 (Box R3336)
    - RF 94061 A 78 - PEPATIAN, INC. - ROMPEFORMA SIXTH ANNUAL FESTIVAL, 1995-1997 (Box R3336)
    - RF 94061 A 79 - APPALSHOP, INC.- AMERICAN FESTIVAL, 1987-1998; 2 folders. (Box R3336)
    - RF 94061 A 79 - APPALSHOP, INC.- AMERICAN FESTIVAL - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1987-1998 (Box R3336)
    - RF 94061 #82 - DANCE THEATER WORKSHOP - SPECIAL UNDERWRITING, RESEARCH AND FRONTIER FUND (S.U.R.F.F.) - 1995-96 SEASON, 1995-1997 (Box R3336)
    - RF 94061 #83 - JACOB'S PILLOW DANCE FESTIVAL - 1996 FESTIVAL SEASON, 1995-1997 (Box R3337)
    - RF 94061 #84 - NATIONAL BLACK ARTS FESTIVAL - 1996 FESTIVAL PROJECT INITIATIVES, 1995-1998 (Box R3337)
    - RF 94061 #85 - LINCOLN CENTER FOR THE PERFORMING ARTS - 1996 LINCOLN CENTER FESTIVAL, 1995-1996 (Box R3337)
    - RF 94064 A 4 - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF LA RAZA - PUBLIC POLICY ANALYSIS, 1980-1997; Total of 8 folders in Boxes R3337 and R3338. (Box R3337)
    - RF 94064 A 4 - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF LA RAZA - PUBLIC POLICY ANALYSIS, 1980-1997; Total of 8 folders in Boxes R3337 and R3338. (Box R3338)
    - RF 94064 A 4 - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF LA RAZA - PUBLIC POLICY ANALYSIS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1980-1997; Total of 6 folders in Boxes R3338 and R3339. (Box R3338)
    - RF 94064 A 4 - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF LA RAZA - PUBLIC POLICY ANALYSIS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1980-1997; Total of 6 folders in Boxes R3338 and R3339. (Box R3339)
    - RF 94054 A 20 - RURAL DEVELOPMENT WOMEN'S CONSULTANCY GROUP (UGANDA) - YOUTH ALIVE CLUB'S ACTIVITIES ON PREVENTING AIDS, 1994-1996 (Box R3340)
    - RF 94060 A 18 - SNITOW-KAUFMAN PRODUCTIONS -VIDEO DOCUMENTARY "BLACKS AND JEWS", 1995-1998 (Box R3340)
    - RF 94060 A 64 - SOUTHERN UNIVERSITY (NEW ORLEANS) ? COMER SCHOOL DEVELOPMENT, 1990-1996 (Box R3340)
    - RF 94069 A 65 - NEW ORLEANS PUBLIC SCHOOLS - COMER SCHOOL DEVELOPMENT, 1992-1996 (Box R3340)
    - RF 94069 #67 - DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA PUBLIC SCHOOLS ? COMER SCHOOL DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM, 1994-1996 (Box R3340)
    - RF 95001 A 320 - SPIC SCIENCE FOUNDATION (INDIA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR V.V. SRIDHAR, 1994-1997 (Box R3340)
- AC.2000.049: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1982-2000; AC.2000.049; 3.6 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3341-R3343.; 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3341-R3343.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.049.1
    - RF 95001 A 329 - TEXAS A&M UNIVERSITY - FERTILE TRANSGENIC RICE PLANTS, 1990-1999; 2 folders. (Box R3341)
    - RF 95001 A 340 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - IMPROVE POWER SUPPLY OF ITS CENTRE FOR PLANT MOLECULAR BIOLOGY, 1994-1999 (Box R3341)
    - RF 95001 A 351 - SOUTH CHINA INSTITUTE OF BOTANY - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR TAO LI ZHENG, 1994-1996 (Box R3341)
    - RF 95001 A 364 - INDIAN INSTITUTE OF SCIENCE - TRAINING IN RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY FOR KUMUDA KUSHALPA AND K.C. NAGARATHNA, 1994-1995 (Box R3341)
    - RF 95001 A 385 - BIOTECHNOLOGY RESEARCH CENTER - CHINESE ACADEMY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES (CHINA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR ZHENG PING, 1995-1999 (Box R3341)
    - RF 95001 A 392 - RESEARCH LABORATORY FOR AGRICULTURAL BIOTECHNOLOGY AND BIOCHEMISTRY (NEPAL) - RICE BREEDING EFFICIENCY, 1989-1997 (Box R3341)
    - RF 95001 A 394 - INSTITUTE OF GENETICS - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR LIANG CHENGZHI, 1995-1997 (Box R3341)
    - RF 95002 #485 - GADJAH MADA UNIVERSITY - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY, 1982-2000; 2 folders. (Box R3342)
    - RF 95003 A 563 - UNIVERSIDAD AUTO NOMA METROPOLITANA ? "URBAN CULTURE IN MEXICO CITY", 1991-1996 (Box R3343)
    - RF 95005 A 67 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - GREEN MANURES AND MAIZE-BEAN CROPPING IN EASTERN AFRICA, 1994-1996 (Box R3343)
    - RF 95005 A 72 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY (KENYA) - HIGHLANDS INITIATIVE IN EASTERN AND CENTRAL AFRICA, 1992-1997 (Box R3343)
    - RF 95005 A 76 - CARE - POPULATION GROWTH AND THE ENVIRONMENT IN UGANDA, 1995-1997 (Box R3343)
    - RF 95006 A 12 - NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH ORGANIZATION (UGANDA) - KAWANDA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE LABORATORY, 1995-1997 (Box R3343)
    - RF 95008 A 15 - SNAPP, SIEGLINDE S. - RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP IN AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES AS MEMBER OF MALAWI MAIZE RESEARCH TEAM, 1993-1996 (Box R3343)
    - RF 95010 A 41 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - MARRIAGE AND CHILDBEARING IN UGANDA, 1994-1999 (Box R3343)
    - RF 95010 A 42 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - WORKSHOP ON INTEGRATING FAMILY PLANNING AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH, 1995-1997 (Box R3343)
    - RF 95010 A 50 - FAYETTEVILLE STATE UNIVERSITY - IRANIAN MARRIAGE AND FERTILITY PATTERNS, WOMEN'S PARTICIPATION IN LABOR FORCE, 1994-1999 (Box R3343)
    - RF 95010 A 51 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - EFFECT OF SOCIAL FACTORS ON WOMEN'S USE OF HEALTH SERVICES, 1994-1996 (Box R3343)
    - RF 95010 A 60 - UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN - CONSEQUENCES OF SEDENTARIZATION AMONG THE RENDILLE OF NORTHERN KENYA, 1995-1996 (Box R3343)